Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1973-2008; 200735
  - Subseries B: Dealers, 204157
    - Leo Malca, 1995-1996; 207316 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Marty Margulies, 1983-1998; 207317 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Stephan Mazoh, 1982-1985; 207318 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Mazzoli, 1981-2001; 207319 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - McNeil, 1982-1988; 207320 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Hans Mayer, 1988-1999; 207321 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Anders Malmberg (International Art), 1981-1986; 207322 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Meyers/Bloom, 1988-1991; 207323 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Valentina Moncada, 1991-2001; 207324 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Milagros Gallery, 1992-1995; 207325 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Richard Milazzo, 1995-1998; 207326 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Minini, 1983; 207327 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - N, 1983-2002; 207328 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - 0, 1979-2000; 207329 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Nathale Obadia, 1993-2000; 207330 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - [N], 1997-2001; 207331 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - [P] [1], 1996; 207332 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Jean-Marc Patras, 1990-2000; 207333 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - [P] [2], 1994-2000; 207334 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - R Persano, 1983-1991; 207335 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - R, 1980-2002; 207336 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - P/Q, 1978-2000; 207337 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Portico, 1981-1984; 207338 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Posters, 1992; 207339 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Giordano Raffaelli - Financial, 1991-1999; 207340 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - [Giordano] Raffaelli, 1991-1998; 207341 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Anita Reiner, 1982-1990; 207342 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Connie Rogers, 1981-1989; 207343 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, 1979-1999; 207344 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Perry Rubensein, 1982-1985; 207345 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Lia Rumma, 1979-1984; 207346 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - [S], 1982-1992; 207347 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - S, 1988-2003; 207348 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Samia Saouma, 1987-1995; 207349 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - [Fabio Sargentini], 1986-1990; 207350 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Alejandro Sales Galeria, 1997-1998; 207351 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Galerie Scheumann & Kluser, 1983; 207352 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Estelle Schwartz, 1980-1994; 207353 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Thomas Segal Gallery, Boston, 1982-1989; 207354 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Sepulveda, 1990-1994; 207355 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Tony Shafrazi, 1993-1995; 207356 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Folker Skulima, 1980-1990; 207357 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Joan Sonnabend, 1978-1983; 207358 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Hans Sonnenberg - Delta Gallery, 1982-1983; 207359 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Specht Galerie, 1988-1991; 207360 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Sperone Westwater Fischer, Inc., 1978-1992; 207361 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Silvana Stipa, 1986-1987; 207362 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - T, 1979-2001; 207363 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Daniel Templon, 1979-1996; 207364 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Daniel Templon; [crossed out] Basquiat Authentication 1997, 1984, 1997; 207365 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Galerie Thomas - Raymond Thomas, 1984-1988; 207366 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Galerie Thomas (Raymond Thomas), 1982-1984; 207367 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Barbara Toll Fine Arts, 1981-1986; 207368 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Sergio Tossi (Prato), 1997; 207369 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - [Regina Trapp], 1981-1983; 207370 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Jan Turner Gallery, 1988-1989; 207371 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - V/W/X, 1976-2000; 207372 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - U/V, 1979-1995; 207373 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Hester Van Royen, 1988-1994; 207374 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Daniel Varenne, 1985-1995; 207375 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Patrick Verelst, 1981-1986; 207376 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Leonora Vega, 1994-1995; 207377 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Viart Corp., 1983-2000; 207378 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - W, 1979-2001; 207379 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Daniel Weinberg Gallery, 1978-1990; 207380 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Gudren Weiss/Galerie Kaess-Weiss, 1997; 207381 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Yajima Gallery, Montreal, 1984-1996; 207382 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Rudolph Zwirner, 1980-1993; 207383 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Y/Z, 1986-2000; 207384 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Subseries C: Museums and Universities, 204158
    Some folder names are followed by the letter 'F,' which denotes that the institution in question is foreign.
    Series comprises correspondence between the gallery and art museums and university-run galleries, as well as other related documents.
    - Museums A, 1984-1998; 207385 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1981-1999; 207386 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Amherst College, 1978; 207387 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - The Center for African Art, 1991; 207388 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Amsterdam - Stedelijk Museum, 1980-1983; 207389 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Art Museum of Americas, 1999; 207390 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Australian National Gallery, 1980-1987; 207391 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Bard College, 1984-1988; 207392 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Basel Kunsthalle, 1983, 1990; 207393 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Basel Kunstmuseum, 1981-1985; 207394 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - University of Berkeley, CA, 1980-1983; 207395 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Bologna (Sassoli), 1993; 207396 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Boston Institute of Contemp. A, 1981-1990; 207397 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Museums - B - University, 1981-2000; 207398 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1982-1986; 207399 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Boston Museum of Fine Art, 1985-1992; 207400 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Bordeaux Musee D'Art Contemp., 1982-1984; 207401 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Broida Museum, 1984; 207402 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - The Brooklyn Museum, 1984-2005; 207403 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Butler Institute of American Art, 1983; 207404 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Museums C, 1981-1997; 207405 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - California Institute of Art, Valencia, 1984-1987; 207406 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Cal Center for the Arts Escondido, 1994-1996; 207407 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - [California State University, Long Beach], 1998; 207408 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - The Chrysler Museum, 1982-1994; 207409 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1983-1994; 207410 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, IL, 1973-1992; 207411 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Museum of Contemp. Art, Chicago, 1981-2000; 207412 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Cornell University Herbert F. Johnson Museum, 1982, 1983, 2000; 207413 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1985-1988; 207414 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Dayton Art Institute, 1982-1983; 207415 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Dallas Museum of Art, 1983-1988; 207416 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Museums - D -, 1979-1994; 207417 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - [Correspondence from Julian Zugazagoitia], 2004; 207418 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Museums - F, 1983-2000; 207419 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Florida Intl University & Florida State University, 1983; 207420 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - [Everson Museum of Art], undated; 207421 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - [George Eastman House], 1987-1988; 207422 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Florida State University, 1981-1982; 207423 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Fort Lauderdale Museum of Art, 1984-1985; 207424 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Fort Worth Museum, 1981-1983; 207426 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Guggenheim Museum, 1979-1993; 207427 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Museums - G, 1982-1995; 207428 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Museums - H, 1984-2003; 207429 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - [Haywood Gallery], 1991; 207430 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Houston Contemp. Arts Museum, 1982-1992; 207431 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Hudson River Museum, 1983-1991; 207432 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - U of Hawaii, 1999; 207433 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Hirshhorn Museum, 1982-1995; 207434 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - I/J, 1985-2000; 207435 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - ICA London, 1983-1991; 207437 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1981-1988; 207438 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Israel Museum F[oreign], 1981-2001; 207439 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Iowa Museum of Art, 1984; 207440 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - K, 1983-2001; 207441 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Joslyn Art Museum, 1984-2001; 207442 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Japan F[oreign], 1983-2000; 207443 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Koln F[oreign], 1983-1984; 207444 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - L, 1983-1994; 207445 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - University of Los Angeles, CA, 1982-1983; 207446 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Musee de L'Elysee Lausanne (Shirin Neshat), 1997; 207447 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - University of Long Beach, CA, 1985-1991; 207448 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Long Island - Fine Arts Museum, 1983-2000; 207449 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Lannan Foundation, 1980-1983, 1991; 207450 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Musee D'Art Moderne Lille Metropole, 1998; 207451 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Kansas, University of, 1983, 1984; 207452 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - London - Royal Academy of Arts F[oreign], 1980, 1981; 207453 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - London - Tate Gallery F[oreign], 1981-1983; 207454 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Los Angeles County Museum, 1982-1995; 207455 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - MoMA N.Y., 1983-2002; 207514 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1982-1984; 207515 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Metropolis, 1990-1991; 207516 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Madison Art Center, 1983, 1987; 207517 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Marquette Univ. - Haggerty Museum, 1986; 207518 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Memphis Brooks Museum of Art, 1984-1987; 207519 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Milwaukee Art Center, 1982-1988; 207520 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Museo de Arte Contem - Monterrey, 1995; 207521 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - N, 1983-1999; 207522 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Musee D'Art Contemporary de Montreal, 1983-1999; 207523 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - New Zealand F[oreign], 1986-1988; 207524 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Aldrich Museum of Contemp. Art, 1985-2003; 207525 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Neuberger Museum, Purchase, N.Y., 1978-1985; 207526 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Newcastle Upon Tyne Polytechnic Art Gallery, 1983, 1984; 207527 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Newport Harbor Art Museum, 1981-1992; 207528 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - New Orleans - Contemporary Mus. of Art, 1985-1987; 207529 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Northern Illinois University, 1984, 1985; 207530 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - New Museum, 1980-1994; 207531 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - New York University; Casa Italiana, 1999; 207532 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - City of New York, Dept. of Cultural Affairs, 1989; 207533 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Art Gallery of Toronto (Kuitca), 1997; 207534 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles MoCA, 1981-1998; 207535 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Los Angeles Instit. of Contemporary Art, 1982-1984; 207536 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Long Beach Museum of Art, 1983-1987; 207537 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - M [1/2], 1984-2001; 207538 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - M [2/2], 1983-1993; 207539 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - M Museum Foreign, 1982-1999; 207540 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Foundation Michetti, 1987-1988; 207541 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Munchen F[oreign], 1983, 1988; 207542 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Ohio - Contemporary Arts Center, 1985; 207543 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Oberlin College, 1980-1983; 207544 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Provincial Museum - Oostend, 1990-1991; 207545 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Fondacion Museo Alejandro Otero, 1995; 207546 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - P/Q, 1980-2001; 207547 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Centre Pompidou F[oreign], 1988-1990; 207548 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Queens Museum, 1985-1987; 207549 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - William Patterson College, 1983; 207550 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1985-1988; 207551 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Pennsylvania Univ. - ICA, 1981-1986; 207552 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Phoenix Art Museum, 1983-1999; 207553 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - R, 1980-1995; 207554 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - S [1], 1983-2003; 207555 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Rotterdam - Museum Boymans F[oreign], 1980-1986; 207556 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - S [2], 1984-1999; 207557 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Savannah State University, 2001-2003; 207558 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Villeurbonne - Le Nouveau Musee; F[oreign], 1983-1999; 207559 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Vizcaya Museum and Gardens, 1980-1983; 207560 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Stedelijk Museum, 1992-1994; 207561 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - St. Louis - Washington Univ., 1990-1992; 207562 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - [Tel Aviv Museum of Art], 1992; 207563 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Tampa Museum, The, 1983; 207564 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - So. Texas, Art Museum of, 1983-1985; 207570 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Museum T Foreign, 1983-1988; 207571 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - T, 1985-1996; 207572 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Texas University - Austin, 1983-1985; 207573 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Texas - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1985, 1990; 207574 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Toledo Museum of Art, 1983, 1999; 207575 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - U/V, 1984-1991; 207576 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1981-2003; 207577 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Adelina von Furstenberg, 1986-1996; 207578 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1985, 1991; 207579 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - W/X, 1983-1996; 207580 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Witte de With - Rotterdam Museum, 1990-1991; 207581 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Y/Z, 1982-1994; 207582 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - [Unlabeled Folder w/ Ieva Mediodia Printed Label], undated; 210202 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Subseries D: Art Fairs/Auction Houses, 204159
    Some folders in this series were grouped together in hanging files that were also named. In those cases, the folder naming convention appears as Name of hanging file: "Name of folder".
    Series comprises correspondence between the gallery and auction houses or organizers of art fairs, as well as other related documents.
    - Christie's: "Christie's Latin America", 1993-2005; 207588 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Christie's: "Christie's 1992-1995", 207589 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Loudmer, 1994; 207590 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Schneider auctions [1/2], 1989-1991; 207591 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Schneider auctions [2/2], 1987-1989; 207592 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Southeby's: "[Untitled]", 1984; 207593 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Southeby's: "Southeby's [1]", 1979-1992; 207594 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Southeby's: "Southeby's [2]", 1992-2000; 207595 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Southeby's: "[Loose Material]", 2002; 207596 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Charbonneaux/Auction Houses: "Perrin, Royere, La Jeunesse", 1993, 1994; 207597 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Charbonneaux/Auction Houses: "Auctions 1992-93", 1992-1993; 207598 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Charbonneaux/Auction Houses: "Charbonneaux Paris", 1987-1990; 207599 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Charbonneaux/Auction Houses: "Villa Grisebach", 2000-2001; 207600 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Charbonneaux/Auction Houses: "[Loose Material]", 1987-1994; 207601 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Miami 1991 - ArtMiami 2000 Jan. 20-25, 1997, 1998; 207602 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Chicago 2001, 207603 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - 1999; Art2000Chicago; May 12-15; 2000; 1997, 1997-2002; 207604 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - 82-86-87-99-89 1990; Chicago Art Fair 1991 92 93 94, 1992-1994; 207605 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Scope 2006 NY, 207606 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - [Loose Material; Auction Houses Antitrust Litigation], 2003-2005; 207607 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Bologna: "Bologna - Arte Fiera 93-94-95; 2001", 1992-2001; 207608 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Bologna: "Fiera Milano 1991", 1990, 1991; 207609 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Bologna: "Bologna 06", 2006; 207615 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Bologna: "Arte Fiera Bologna 96", 2007; 207616 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Bologna: "Arte Fiera Bologna 07", 2007; 207617 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Bologna: "Bologna 07", 2007; 207618 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Bologna: "[Loose Material]", 2006-2008; 207619 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Arco Art Fair Madrid 1989, 1984-1989; 207620 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Arco/February 11-16th 1999, 1988, 1989; 207621 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - [Loose Material - Art Cologne 1995], 207622 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Basel: "Basel Art Fair - June 1994/95 [99]", 1994, 1995, 2005; 207623 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Basel: "Basel Art Fair ['87]-1983", 1987-1993; 207624 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Basel: "[Loose Material]", undated; 207625 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Documenta: "Buenos Aires Art Fair 1995", 207626 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Documenta: "Cologne[Crossed Out] Art Fair; Hamburg/Zurich", 1988; 207627 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Documenta: "FIAC 90-1991", 1991-1993; 207628 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Documenta: "Documenta 1982-3", 1982-1983; 207629 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Guadalajara: "Atlanta Fine Art Fairs", 1990-1991; 207639 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Documenta: "Stockholm Art Fair 1982 1983-19894", 1981-1984; 207640 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Guadalajara: "1985 Zurich Art Fair Forum", 207641 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Guadalajara: "Venezia Biennale; Paris Biennale; San Paolo Biennale; Sydney Biennale", 1983, 1984; 207642 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Guadalajara: "Guadalajara 1996 - September", 207643 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Subseries E: Magazines, Critics, and Curators, 204160
    Series comprises correspondence between the gallery and magazines (usually regarding advertisements), art critics, and individual curators; as well as other related documents.
    Folder labelled "Fire '88," which was originally filed at the end of Series II, Subseries E, has been moved to Series VII, Subseries C.
    - A, 1979-1995; 207644 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Arts, 1982-1990; 207645 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Flashart, 1981-1992; 207646 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Artforum, 1980-1992; 207647 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Artnews, 1980-1996; 207648 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - B, 1982-1985; 207649 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Artscribe, 1982-1988; 207650 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Artfactum, 1985-1989; 207651 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Art and Auction, 1982-1991; 207652 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - [A], 1981-1988; 207653 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Art in America, 1981-1989; 207654 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - C, 1985-1995; 207655 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - D, 1979-1991; 207656 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - E, 1985-1989; 207658 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - J, 1985-1989; 207659 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Interview Magazine, 1984-1989; 207660 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - K, 1982-1989; 207661 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - L, 1986-1991; 207662 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Lambarelli, 1986-1996; 207663 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - M, 1983-1989; 207664 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - New York Times, 1988-1996; 207665 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - N, 1981-1995; 207698 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - [T/U/V], 1982-1995; 207699 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - The Village Voice, 1980-1888; 207700 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - V, 1988-1995; 207701 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - S, 1981-1995; 207702 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - O, 1982-1991; 207703 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - P, 1981-1996; 207704 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - R, 1982-1989; 207705 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Series III: Artist Files, 1963-2004; 200736
  Series comprises paper documents (including artists' bios, price lists, clippings, correspondence, exhibition announcements) and photographic materials relating to artists represented by the gallery and shows held at the gallery.
  - Subseries A: General Artist Files, 204161
    Subseries comprises files kept by Annina Nosei Gallery on artists both represented and not represented by the gallery. Materials include clippings, gallery-produced artist's biographies, photographs, correspondence, and exhibition announcements and other promotional material.
    Folders in this subseries were stored in two different ways: the majority filed alphabetically in filing cabinets and the rest filed by artist in cardboard boxes and letter boxes. Since, according to Annina Nosei, the only reason for the different filing systems was lack of space in the filing cabinets, folders from boxes are interfiled alphabetically with the folders from the filing cabinets.
    - A, 1978,1988; 207707 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - John Ahearn, 1980-1983; 207708 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Jean-Michel Alberola, 1982; 207709 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - James Aldridge, 1999; 207710 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Vicky Alexander Tel. Home 925 5819, 1987-1988; 207711 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Ghada Amer, 1993-1999; 207712 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Carl Andre, 1978-1983; 207713 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Karel Appel - Reviews Press, 1984-1985; 207714 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Karel Appel Poster, 1984; 207715 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Karel Appel - Correspondence, 1984-1986; 207716 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Dan Asher, 1985-1989; 207717 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - B, 1976-1991; 207718 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Donald Baechler, 1980, 1981; 207735 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Artists A-B Misc., 1999; 207719 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Jack Barth, 1981-1989; 207720 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat] [1/4], 1981-1983; 207721 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat] [2/4], 1982-1983; 207722 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat] [3/4], 1982; 207723 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat] [4/4], 1982-1983; 207724 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - William Beckley, 1980-1981; 207725 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Jose Bedia, 1999; 207726 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Veronique Bellavista, 1995, 2000; 207727 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Benzaken, 1991-2002; 207728 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Jose Maria Bermejo, 1983-1992; 207729 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Francois Boisrond, 1982-1985; 207730 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Troy Brauntuch, 1980-1987; 207731 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Dino Bruzzone, 2000-2001; 207732 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Mike Bidlo, 1985; 207733 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Nancy Bowen - Accounting, 1988-1994; 207734 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Nancy Bowen - Press, 1983-1994; 207736 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Beth Brenner, 1987-1989; 207737 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Beth Brenner - Correspondence, 1987-1991; 207738 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - David Bowes - Press + Correspondence, 1982-1991; 207739 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Ellen Brooks - Correspondence, 1987-1989; 207740 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Ellen Brooks [1], 1987-1992; 207741 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Ellen Brooks [2], 1987-1989; 207742 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Ellen Brooks - Damaged Frames Paperwork, 1989; 207743 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Ellen Brooks Finances 1989, 1987-1989; 207744 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - C, 1976-1996; 207745 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Juan Cambre, 1991-1993; 207746 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Loren Calaway, 1980-1984; 207747 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Pizzi Canella Show Cards, 1985-1992; 207748 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Canella; Correspondence with Collectors, Galleries, Institutions, 1991-1993; 207749 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Pizzi Cannella Press, 1985; 207750 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Pizzi Cannella, 1985-1993; 207751 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Pizzi Cannella - Correspondence, 1985-1992; 207752 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Fernando Canovas Press Release; Biography, 1995-1999; 207753 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Fernando Canovas Correspondence 1995-2002, 207754 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Fernando Canovas Reviews/Show Cards, 1995-2000; 207755 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Luciano Castelli [Folder from "Salomé + Castelli Letter Box], 1981-1983; 207756 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Bruno Ceccobelli [1], 1985, 1989; 207757 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Bruno Ceccobelli [2], 1987-1993; 207758 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Chiaraluce, undated; 207759 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Guiseppe Chiari, 1994; 207760 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Peter Chevalier, 1983; 207761 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Abraham David Christian, 1998-1999; 207762 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Francesco Clemente, 1978-1980; 207763 (Box 24, Folder 28)